
const ForComputer = [
	{
		id:1,
		Question:"Who is the Brain of any Computer ?",
		A:"ALU",
		B:"Memory",
		C:"CPU",
		D:"Control Unit",
		Ans:"C"
	},
	{
		id:2,
		Question:"Gigabyte is equal to _____________?",
		A:"1024 bit",
		B:"1000 Megabytes",
		C:"1024 Kilobytes",
		D:"1024 Megabytes",
		Ans:"D"
	},
	{
		id:3,
		Question:"the Basic operation performed by a Computer are _________ ?",
		A:"Arithmetic Oparetion",
		B:"Logical Oparetion",
		C:"storage and Relative",
		D:"All the above",
		Ans:"D"
	},
	{
		id:4,
		Question:"WWW stand for ______ ?",
		A:"World Wide Wed",
		B:"Wide World Wed",
		C:"Wed World Wide",
		D:"World Whole Web",
		Ans:"A"
	},
	{
		id:5,
		Question:"Who is the Father of Computer ?",
		A:"Allen Turing",
		B:"Charles Baddge",
		C:"Simur Cray",
		D:"Augusta Adaming",
		Ans:"B"
	},
	{
		id:6,
		Question:"Who is the Father of Internet ?",
		A:"Simur Cray",
		B:"Danis Riche",
		C:"Vint Cerf",
		D:"Martin Cooper",
		Ans:"C"
	},
	{
		id:7,
		Question:"ALU stand for ________ ?",
		A:"Arithmetic Logic Unit",
		B:"Array Logic Unit",
		C:"Application Logic Unit",
		D:"None of above",
		Ans:"A"
	},
	{
		id:8,
		Question:"Who is the Father of Computer Science ?",
		A:"Simur Cray",
		B:"Charles Baddge",
		C:"Allen Turing",
		D:"Augusta Adaming",
		Ans:"C"
	},
	{
		id:9,
		Question:"Junk E-Mail is also called _________ ?",
		A:"Spam",
		B:"Spoof",
		C:"Sniffer Script",
		D:"Spool",
		Ans:"A"
	},
	{
		id:10,
		Question:"A Computer cannot 'Boot' if it does not have the ______ ?",
		A:"Compiler",
		B:"Loader",
		C:"Assembler",
		D:"Oparetioning System",
		Ans:"D"
	},
]


export {ForComputer};